Inventory of the Francis E. Warren Papers, 1867-1974
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
Francis E. Warren papers
1867-1974
Warren, Francis E. (Francis Emroy), 1844-1929
00013
125.85 cubic ft. (301 boxes) + artifacts
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
Collection includes letterpress books containing political, personal and business correspondence; financial records from most of his businesses; personal, political and business correspondence;, political and personal scrapbooks; clippings; and miscellaneous other material.
Francis E. Warren, a Massachusetts native, emigrated to Wyoming in 1868. He began work in the mercantile business, soon becoming a partner and then owner of several businesses and ranching properties. While increasing his business holdings, Warren became involved in politics and government. He was a governor of the Wyoming Territory and the first governor of the state of Wyoming. He stepped down as governor after being elected one of Wyoming's first United States senators. Warren was a leader in Wyoming politics and business and in the U.S. Senate until his death in 1929.
Francis Emroy Warren was born in Hinsdale, Berkshire County, Massachusetts, on June 20, 1844. He attended public schools and Hinsdale Academy. At the outbreak of the Civil War he enlisted in Company C, Forty-ninth Regiment, Massachusetts Volunteer Infantry, and served as a private and non-commissioned officer. He received the Congressional Medal of Honor "for gallantry on the battlefield at the siege of Port Hudson".
In 1868 Warren emigrated to Wyoming, which was then a part of the Dakota Territory, where he worked in a furniture store for another Massachusetts native, A. R. Converse. By 1871 he became a partner, with the firm's name changing to Converse and Warren. In 1877 he bought Converse out and changed the company's name to F. E. Warren and Company, later Warren Mercantile Company.
In 1883 Warren formed the Warren Live Stock Company which grew to be one of the most important ranching operations in the state, encompassing some 150,000 deeded acres. Warren owned several parcels of real estate in Wyoming and a number of other companies including the Cheyenne and Northern Railroad and the Brush-Swan Electric Company, which provided the first electric power to Cheyenne.
In addition to his business interests, Warren was active in politics. He was a member of the Cheyenne City Council from 1873 to 1874 and was instrumental in securing the first lighting system for Cheyenne. In 1873 he was elected to the Council of the Territorial Assembly, where he served from 1873 to 1874 and from 1884 to 1885. He was council president during his first term.
Warren served as territorial treasurer in 1876, 1879, 1882, and 1884, and as chairman of the Republican Territorial Central Committee. He was elected mayor of Cheyenne in 1885 and was appointed territorial governor of Wyoming by President Chester A. Arthur to fill the unexpired term of William Hale. He took the oath of office February 28, 1885.
During his tenure Warren called for federal troops to protect Chinese workers during the riots in Rock Springs, Wyoming, on September 2, 1885. He also instituted a quarantine on cattle from all states and territories in which a pleuro-pneumonia was thought to have existed. He served as governor until November 11, 1886, when he was removed from office by President Grover Cleveland.
Warren was a delegate to the Republican National Convention at Chicago in 1888. He was appointed territorial governor for a second time by President Benjamin Harrison, taking the oath of office April 9, 1889, and serving until October 11, 1890, when he was elected the first governor of the State of Wyoming. He took office on October 11, 1890, and resigned November 24, 1890, after having been elected by the State Legislature as one of the first two U.S. Senators from Wyoming. He served until 1893 and was reelected in 1895 and served until his death in 1929.
From his first term in the Senate, Warren was one of its leaders. Between 1891 and 1893 and 1895 and 1899 he served as chair of the Committee on Irrigation and Reclamation of Public Lands. He worked closely with Wyoming's other senator, Joseph M. Carey, in supporting the Carey Act for the reclamation of public land. Following the passage of this act, Wyoming was the first state to begin the reclamation of arid land. In 1896 Warren offered an amendment to the rivers and harbors bill which provided funding for a survey of rivers in Wyoming and Colorado to determine reservoir sites. Along with Carey, Warren was known as a founding father of irrigation in the West.
Warren served as chair of the Military Affairs Committee from 1905 to 1911. During that period he worked with Secretary of War Elihu Root to reorganize the army, raise military pay, and establish a General Staff. As the ranking minority member prior to World War I, he supported the national defense and the selective service acts.
From 1921 until 1929, Senator Warren was chairman of the Appropriations Committee, one of the most important Senate committees. Here he supported reduced government expenditures and stiffer tariffs, especially those which protected the farm and livestock industries.
At his death on November 24, 1929, in Washington, D.C., Warren had served as Senator for thirty-seven years, the longest service record in the United States Senate to that time.
Francis E. Warren married Helen M. Smith on January 26, 1871, and before her death in 1902 they had two children, Helen Frances (Frankie) and Frederick Emroy. Senator Warren was remarried on June 28, 1911, to Clara LeBaron Morgan.
Helen married General John J. Pershing. Fred E. Warren became vice-president of Warren Live Stock Company in 1913 and replaced his father as president upon his death in 1929. He retained this position until his own death in 1949. Fred Warren was followed by his son Francis Emroy.
To maintain control of his many business interests while away from home, Warren relied heavily on two men. W.W. Gleason was general manager of Warren Live Stock and ran the operation while Warren was in Washington, D.C. Hiram Sapp was Warren's executive secretary and served as liaison between Warren and his companies and acted as a troubleshooter while Warren attended the Senate.
The papers include gubernatorial papers (1885-1892); senatorial papers (1890-1945); the records of: Warren Livestock Company (1884-1957); Guiterman and Warren (1878-1880); Miner and Warren (1878-1883); Post and Warren (1880-1884); Brush-Swan Electric Light Co., Cheyenne City Gas Co., and Cheyenne Light, Fuel and Power (1882-1905); Cheyenne Black Hills and Montana Railway Co. (1883-1889); Cheyenne Carriage Co. (1883-1900); Cheyenne Street Railroad Co. (1887-1907); Wyoming Phonograph Co. (1889-1891); Cheyenne Investment Co. (1889-1911); Warren Irrigation Co. (1909-1915); Cheyenne Hotels Co. (1910-1913); Cheyenne Securities Co. (1910-1961); A.R. Converse (1867-1874); Converse and Warren (1874-1878); F.E. Warren Company (1878-1883); F.E. Warren Mercantile Co. (1883-1961); and others. Also included are papers of F.E. Warren's son, Fred E. Warren; correspondence with Francis E. Warren's daughter Helen and son-in-law General John J. Pershing; and one series of papers of W.W. Gleason, manager of the Warren Livestock Company.
Also included are papers of F.E. Warren's son, Fred E. Warren; correspondence with Francis E. Warren's daughter Helen and son-in-law General John J. Pershing; and one series of papers of W.W. Gleason, manager of the Warren Livestock Company.
The Francis E. Warren Papers, 1868-1974, include political, business and personal material. There are letterpress copybooks, financial books, scrapbooks, correspondence and photographs documenting F. E. Warren's political, business and personal life.
Political material includes scrapbooks of F. E. Warren's political life, general correspondence as well as government letterpress copybooks, military affairs and congressional reports. Information on the Johnson County War is included as well as telegrams in code.
The history of Warren Live Stock Company, located in Cheyenne, Wyoming, is documented in journals, ledgers, and day and cash books, leases and legal and financial material. Includes federal government papers investigating enclosure of public lands and the 1906 fencing case against Warren. W. W. Gleason's personal papers are also included. Much of the correspondence with the company is in telegrams.
F. E. Warren's other business interests are documented in record books and correspondence concerning his many companies. The largest of these, in addition to Warren Live Stock Company, are F. E. Warren Mercantile, Cheyenne Securities Company and Cheyenne Hotel Company, which owned the Plains Hotel and Opera House.
Personal materials include F. E. Warren's correspondence with his son, Fred, first wife, Helen, and other personal and general correspondence. There are estate, legal and financial documents, as well as newspaper clippings and scrapbooks of invitations. Box 19, folder 4, contains papers related to F. E. Warren's decorated service during the Civil War.
There are no access restrictions on the materials for research purposes, and the collection is open to the public.
There are no known other archival collections created by Francis E. Warren at the date of processing.
Acquisition Information
The bulk of the F.E. Warren Collection was given to the American Heritage Center in two groups, the first in 1940 and the second in 1944. Small additions have been made since that time, and preliminary processing was done.
In 1992 the collection was reprocessed by a team of student interns. Material has been organized in groups and series according to original indications wherever possible. Two cubic feet of bills and receipts and one cubic foot of printed material have been separated. The material has been microfilmed for preservation.
In October 1995, a second addendum of materials were donated to the American Heritage Center by Mrs. Paul Smith and Evelyna Smith Herman. This material has been arranged alphabetically. This material has not been microfilmed.
More material for this collection was received from Janet Reed Dodson in July 2020.
Existence and Location of Copies
Digital reproductions of select material from this collection are available at http://digitalcollections.uwyo.edu:8180/luna/servlet/uwydbuwy~71~71.
Access Terms
Gleason, W. W.; Warren, Frederick E.; Pershing, John J. (John Joseph), 1860-1948.; Warren Livestock Company.; F.E. Warren Mercantile Company.; Guiterman and Warren.; Miner and Warren.; Post and Warren.; Brush-Swan Electric Light Company.; Cheyenne City Gas Company.; Cheyenne Light, Fuel and Power.; Cheyenne, Black Hills and Montana Railway Company.; Cheyenne Carriage Company.; Cheyenne Street Railroad Company.; Wyoming Photograph Company.; Cheyenne Investment Company.; Warren Irrigation Company.; Cheyenne Securities Company.; A.R. Converse Co.; Converse and Warren.; F.E. Warren Company.; Wyoming. Governor (1885-1890: Warren); Cattle trade-Wyoming.; Sheep ranches--Wyoming.; Teapot Dome Scandal, 1921-1924.; Fences--Law and legislation--Wyoming.; Wyoming--History--to 1889.; Wyoming--History--1890-1918.; Wyoming--History--1919-1945.; Wyoming--History--1946-; Wyoming--Genealogy.; Businessmen – United States; Politicians – United States; Letterpress copy books; Photographs
Ranching; Business, Industry, Labor, and Commerce; Politics, Government, and Law; Laws and Legislation; Politics and Politicians; Territorial Government; Wyoming
Container List
- Series I. Political Papers, 1878-1945
  - Subseries 1. General Correspondence, 1890-1929; 21.5 cubic ft. (113 books).
    Arranged chronologically. Letterpress copybooks including political, business and personal correspondence.
    - Nov. 28, 1890-Feb. 6, 1891, microfilm reel 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Feb. 6, 1891-June 11, 1891, microfilm reel 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - June 11, 1891-Dec. 10, 1891, microfilm reel 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Dec. 10, 1891-Feb. 20, 1892, microfilm reel 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Feb. 20, 1892-Mar. 31, 1892, microfilm reel 3 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Mar. 31, 1892-May 17, 1892, microfilm reel 3 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - May 17, 1892-Aug. 8, 1892, microfilm reel 4 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Aug. 24, 1892-Mar. 20, 1893, microfilm reel 4 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Sept. 13, 1895-June 13, 1896, microfilm reel 5 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Apr. 10, 1895-Jan. 8, 1896, microfilm reel 5 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Jan. 9, 1896-Apr. 11, 1896, microfilm reel 6 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Apr. 12, 1896-Feb. 27, 1897, microfilm reel 7 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Feb. 27, 1897-Jan. 27, 1898, microfilm reel 8 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Mar. 9, 1897-May. 26, 1897, microfilm reel 9 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - May 24, 1897-Dec. 29, 1897, microfilm reel 10 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Jan. 27, 1898-Dec. 6, 1898; microfilm reel 11 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Jan. 7, 1898-Apr. 18, 1898; microfilm reel 12 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Apr. 19, 1898-Jan. 3, 1899; microfilm reel 13 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, July 23, 1898-Aug. 9, 1899; microfilm reel 14 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Jan. 2, 1899-May 4, 1899; microfilm reel 15 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Dec. 1, 1899-Apr. 30, 1900; microfilm reel 16 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Dec. 25, 1899-May 13, 1901,Nov. 12, 1901-Mar. 18, 1903,Dec. 24, 1902-Jan. 1, 1903, Feb. 7, 1903-; microfilm reel 17 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Aug. 4, 1899-Mar. 23, 1900; microfilm reel 18 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Mar. 23, 1900-Jan. 3, 1901; microfilm reel 19 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, May 12, 1900-Dec. 17, 1900; microfilm reel 20 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Jan. 1, 1901-Feb. 24, 1901; microfilm reel 21 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Feb. 24, 1901-May 6, 1901; microfilm reel 22 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, May 6, 1901-Oct. 25, 1901; microfilm reel 23 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Oct. 26, 1901-Mar. 17, 1902; microfilm reel 24 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Mar. 18, 1902-July 24, 1902; microfilm reel 25 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, July 24, 1902-Feb. 9, 1903; microfilm reel 26 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, July 10, 1902-July 30, 1902,Nov. 21, 1902-Nov. 30, 1902,Jan. 15, 1903-July 30, 1903; microfilm reel 27 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, microfilm reel 28; July 29, 1903-Feb. 13, 1904 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Feb. 12, 1904-July 31, 1904; microfilm reel 29 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, July 31, 1904-Jan. 29, 1905; microfilm reel 30 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Jan. 29, 1905-May 5, 1905; microfilm reel 31 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, May 4, 1905-Dec. 6, 1905; microfilm reel 32 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Dec. 5, 1905-Mar. 13, 1906; microfilm reel 33 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Mar. 13, 1906-June 19, 1906; microfilm reel 34 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, June 19, 1906-Dec. 4, 1906; microfilm reel 35 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Nov. 17, 1906-Feb. 23, 1907; microfilm reel 36 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Feb. 18, 1907-May 1, 1907; microfilm reel 37 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Apr. 18, 1903-May 20, 1903,Oct. 16, 1903-Nov. 7, 1903,May 3, 1904-Dec. 13, 1904,May 25, 1905-Nov. 26, 1905,June 18, 1907-Oct. 21, 1907; microfilm reel 38 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, June 5, 1907-Jan. 15, 1908; microfilm reel 39 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Jan. 14, 1908-Mar. 13, 1908; microfilm reel 40 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Mar. 11, 1908-May 25, 1908; microfilm reel 41 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, May 26, 1908-Oct. 7, 1908; microfilm reel 42 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Oct. 7, 1908-Jan. 22, 1909; microfilm reel 43 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Jan. 21, 1909-Apr. 21, 1909; microfilm reel 44 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Apr. 6, 1909-July 7, 1909; microfilm reel 45 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, July 7, 1909-Dec. 6, 1909; microfilm reel 46 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Oct. 23, 1909-Mar. 8, 1910; microfilm reel 47 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Mar. 7, 1910-May 29, 1910; microfilm reel 48 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, May 29, 1910-Sept. 13, 1910; microfilm reel 49 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Aug. 26, 1910-Jan. 28, 1911; microfilm reel 50 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Jan. 22, 1911-Apr. 6, 1911; microfilm reel 51 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Apr. 5, 1911-June 13, 1911; microfilm reel 52 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, June 12, 1911-Aug. 10, 1911; microfilm reel 53 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Aug. 8, 1911-Dec. 1, 1911; microfilm reel 54 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Nov. 21, 1911-Feb. 6, 1912; microfilm reel 55 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Feb. 5, 1912-Apr. 2, 1912; microfilm reel 56 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Mar. 28, 1912-May 28, 1912; microfilm reel 57 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, May 25, 1912-Aug. 7, 1912; microfilm reel 58 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Aug. 7, 1912-Oct. 29, 1912; microfilm reel 59 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Oct. 31, 1912-Feb. 1, 1913; microfilm reel 60 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Feb. 3, 1913-Apr. 25, 1913; microfilm reel 61 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Apr. 22, 1913-Aug. 30, 1913; microfilm reel 62 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Aug. 30, 1913-Jan. 15, 1914; microfilm reel 63 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Jan. 16, 1914-Mar. 31, 1914; microfilm reel 64 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Mar. 31, 1914-July 6, 1914; microfilm reel 65 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, July 6, 1914-Jan. 20, 1915; microfilm reel 66 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, June 21, 1915-Aug. 26, 1915; microfilm reel 67 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Apr. 16, 1915-Dec. 2, 1915; microfilm reel 67 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Aug. 27, 1915-Mar. 4, 1916; microfilm reel 68 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Mar. 4, 1916-June 27, 1916; microfilm reel 69 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, June 28, 1916-Dec. 21, 1916; microfilm reel 70 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Dec. 21, 1916-Feb. 10, 1917; microfilm reel 71 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Feb. 8, 1917-Mar. 27, 1917; microfilm reel 71 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Mar. 26, 1917-June 18, 1917; microfilm reel 72 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, June 18, 1917-Oct. 30, 1917; microfilm reel 73 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Oct. 30, 1917-Mar. 19, 1918; microfilm reel 74 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Mar. 18, 1918-June 17, 1918; microfilm reel 75 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, June 17, 1918-Sept. 10, 1918; microfilm reel 76 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Sept. 9, 1918-Nov. 12, 1918; microfilm reel 77 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Nov. 13, 1918-Feb. 15, 1919; microfilm reel 78 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Feb. 14, 1919-June 12, 1919; microfilm reel 79 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, June 13, 1919-Oct. 6, 1919; microfilm reel 80 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Oct. 6, 1919-Feb. 11, 1920; microfilm reel 81 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Feb. 10, 1920-June 23, 1920; microfilm reel 82 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, June 17, 1920-Jan. 8, 1921; microfilm reel 83 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Jan. 8, 1921-Apr. 14, 1921; microfilm reel 84 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Apr. 14, 1921-July 22, 1921; microfilm reel 85 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, July 23, 1921-Nov. 22, 1921; microfilm reel 86 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Nov. 22, 1921-Mar. 14, 1922; microfilm reel 87 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Mar. 14, 1922-July 15, 1922; microfilm reel 88 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, July 15, 1922-Jan. 4, 1923; microfilm reel 89 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Jan. 4, 1923-Apr. 27, 1923; microfilm reel 90 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Apr. 26, 1923-Oct. 15, 1923; microfilm reel 91 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Oct. 15, 1923-Feb. 16, 1924; microfilm reel 92 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Feb. 16, 1924-May 22, 1924; microfilm reel 93 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, May 22, 1924-Sept. 20, 1924; microfilm reel 94 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Sept. 20, 1924-Jan. 28, 1925; microfilm reel 95 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Jan. 28, 1925-June 2, 1925; microfilm reel 96 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, June 2, 1925-Jan. 4, 1926; microfilm reel 97 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, June 11, 1925-Apr. 2. 1926; microfilm reel 98 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Apr. 2, 1926-Oct. 18, 1926; microfilm reel 99 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Oct. 16, 1926-Apr. 4, 1927; microfilm reel 100 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Apr. 4, 1927-Dec. 9, 1927; microfilm reel 101 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, July 25, 1927-Apr. 4, 1928; microfilm reel 102 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Apr. 3, 1928-Oct. 29, 1928; microfilm reel 103 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, June 30, 1928-Feb. 23, 1929; microfilm reel 104 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Feb. 27, 1929-Aug. 12, 1929; microfilm reel 105 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, June 5, 1929-Sept. 5, 1929; microfilm reel 106 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence: Letterbook, Aug. 13, 199-Dec. 10, 1929; microfilm reel 106 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 2. General Business Correspondence, 1878-1932; 5 cubic ft. (28 books)
    - General Business Correspondence: Letterbook, Aug. 3, 1878-June 31, 1880; microfilm reel 107 (Box 22, Folder 3)